<resources>

    <string name="pdfYourRecentMeasurement">
Your recent measurement at</string>
    <string name="emptySpace">\n</string>
    <string name="pdfFixedText">Hemoglobin information:\n\n
1.	Hemoglobin value is low: More commonly seen in female, also commonly known as anemia.\n
2.	In symptoms such as dizziness, fatigue, tarry stool, or blood stool, it is recommended to go to the hospital for further examination.\n
3.	It is recommended to consume more iron rich and protein rich foods, and also vitamin-C, it helps iron absorption.\n
4.	Hemoglobin value is high: Blood is concentrated, and harder to flow. It is recommended to go to hospital for further examination.\n\n
        Health IndexReference:\n\n
1.	Blood Glucose Level\n
o	Fasting/Preprandial: 3.9~6.1 mmol/L (70~110 mg/dl)\n
o	2 hr postprandial: 3.9~7.8 mmol/L (70~140 mg/dl)\n
2.	Pulse\n
o	60-100 bpm \n
3.	Blood Flow Velocity\n
o	220~440 AU \n
4.	Hemoglobin\n
o	male: 120-160 g/L\n
o	female: 110-150 g/L\n
5.	Oxygen Saturation \n
94% - 100%\n\n
        Other Health Index data:\n\n
Glucose information: \n\n
When BGL value is too low or too high,\n
1.	First check that the smart sensor is used under suitable testing conditions.\n
2.	Blood glucose should not be lower than 100mg/dL, it is recommended to replenish body sugar by eating piece of candy and cookie to avoid low blood sugar.\n
3.	Blood glucose should not be above 300mg/dL, make sure no symptoms such as dizziness or vomiting occur. Drink plenty of water and test again after one hour.\n
4.	If blood glucose is above 300 mg/dL, it is recommended to go hospital for further examination.\n\n
        Pulse information:\n\n
When Pulse value is low or high,\n
1.	Pulse value is low: lower than 60bpm, commonly seen in atrioventricular block or increased intracranial pressure.\n
2.	Pulse value is high: more than 100bpm, commonly seen in fever, anemia, or coronary heart diseases.\n
3.	It is usually companied with other physical symptoms, it is recommended to go hospital for further examination.\n\n
        Blood Flow Velocity information:\n\n
        1.	BFV value is denoted as the unit time flown through a section of the blood vessel, also called "volume rate".\n
2.	Arterial blood flow is affected by systolic and diastolic heartbeat. Systolic heartbeat speeds up the blood flow, and diastolic heartbeat slows down the blood flow. \n
3.	When blood vessel is elastic, blood flow is slower; When blood vessel becomes stuff, blood flow will be significantly faster. \n
4.	We can use the values derived from this testing to compare the blood flow of a person of similar age, and therefore deduce whether the person\'s blood vessel is aged faster than the actual person\'s age.\n\n
How to keep your blood vessels elastic:\n\n
1.	Maintain constant exercise.\n
2.	Maintain balanced nutrition intake such as proteins and vitamins.\n
3.	Regulate three highs: blood glucose, blood pressure, and blood fat.\n
4.	Drink enough water daily to reduce blood vessel stickiness.\n\n

         Oxygen Saturation(SpO2) Information:\n\n
 1.Less than 94percent: Lack of Oxygen.\n
 2.Less than 90percent: Hypoxemia.\n
 3.In case of SpO2 less than 90percent, and shows symptoms of stuffy chest, fatigue and difficulty in breathing, it is recommended to go to hospital for examination.
    </string>
    <string name="pdfFile">pdf file</string>
    <string name="esserHealthCareTechnology">ESER Health Care Digital Technology Co Ltd</string>
    <string name="healthAlert">Health Alert</string>
    <string name="applicationPdf">application/pdf</string>
    <string name="pdfPulse">Pulse -</string>
    <string name="bpm">bpm</string>
    <string name="pdfBloodFlow">Blood flow velocity - </string>
    <string name="au">AU</string>
    <string name="pdfOxygenSaturation">Oxygen saturation -</string>
    <string name="pdfHemoglobin">Hemoglobin -</string>
    <string name="pdfBloodGlucose">Blood glucose -</string>
    <string name="pdfHello">Hello</string>
    <string name="resultScrenshot">Result Screenshot</string>
    <string name="applicationExcel">application/excel</string>
    <string name="excelFileText"> History Data</string>

</resources>
